Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. This is the first time I saw it. It was said that it was very special. It was very special. This is the second special place. It is a special place. They are from Dongbei, Dongbei. They are from Changshang. Now, let's look at it. There is a second place.
good good good good good good good good good good
I'm a little nervous. Did you say that the first time you came to the TV show? The first time you came to the TV show, there will be a little nervous. You see, there are so many things to remember. There are so many things to remember. There are so many things to remember. Let's talk about the next time we come to the TV show. The next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to the TV show, the next time we come to
My name is Bai Yun. My name is Heitou. My name is Heitou. My name is Wu. My name is Wu. My name is Wu. My name is Lao Hong. My name is Lao Mu.
Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone.
I'm not saying that I'm not saying that I'm not saying that I'm not saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that I'm saying that
I don't know where it is today. I said that we are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past. We are going back to the past.
What are you doing here? Let's talk about it. I'm going to prepare for it. Are you ready? I'm ready to go out and go out. I'm going out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out and go out
Mom, are you ready? Yes, I'm ready. Wait for me. What's the problem? Brother, I've been waiting for you for a long time. I've been waiting for you for a long time. I've been waiting for you for a long time. I've been waiting for you for a long time.
What kind of person is that? What kind of conversation is this? What kind of conversation is this? When we talk about the topic of the topic, we don't talk about the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic of the topic
We have to do the same thing. We have to do the same thing. We have to do the same thing. Do the same thing.
In the 1980s, the two-year-old, Hong-shui, was very rich. The White House, and the White House, was also very rich. There were also people's troops, and they were also very hard-working. The state of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State of the State
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
I don't know. What did he say? He said that he said that he was a teacher. He was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher. He said that he was a teacher.
Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry.
Look at you. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money. You don't have money.
What are you talking about? What are you talking about? That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right
They are so scared. They are so scared. They are so scared. Don't say anything. Don't say anything. We are still talking about you, right? Now, I will ask you the details. Which day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day? The day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the day of the
This is what you see. This is the first time. In fact, you should have this kind of thought. Of course, I used to say that when I was a kid, it was almost over. That's right. You don't want to say that. You want to bring me back to your old house. You can write it down if I can write it down. What will you write? This is called writing.
This is the most important thing. I don't think it's a coincidence. I think it's not a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence. I don't think it's a coincidence.
Uncle, it's not right to say so. Actually, my mom is still looking at you. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now. It's not easy now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I remember I gave you a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper, a piece of paper,
I don't want to talk about it, I don't want to talk about it, I don't want to talk about it, I don't want to talk about it, I don't want to talk about it, I don't want to talk about it, I don't want to talk about it, I don't want to talk about it,
When I was in the morning, I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen. I was in the kitchen.
It's not that there's a person in this world. I'm afraid it's a girl. Yes, I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat. I'm afraid that the person in this world is like a cat.
I heard that I'm here. I don't have a problem in this movie. I think there's a difference between the two of us. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
There's nothing like that. There's nothing like that. But let's say that the parents of the parents have so many years. Listen carefully. I think this is the way to remember this. We know that our young students are our students. This is the way to remember this. And we've been working together for a long time. Now, how do you feel? When we open the door, we'll be able to open the door for two hours.
It's been a long time since I was a child, and I have to ask for a question. I said that it was a long time ago. It was a long time ago. It was a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago. It's a long time ago.
I would like to ask you a question. A question? A question? A question? A question? A question? A question? A question? A question?
I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you! I'm so proud of you!
You are so young. You are so young. You are so young. You are so young. I think I don't know. He didn't want to come back to the country. He asked us to go to the countryside and go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside. He asked us to go to the countryside.
Can you tell me what happened in the previous video? I'll tell you what happened in the previous video. I'll tell you what happened in the previous video. I'll tell you what happened in the previous video. I'll tell you what happened in the previous video.
I'm so happy to see you again. I'm so happy to see you again. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today. I'm so happy to see you again today.
Let's talk about the show today. I think it's a very serious topic. Let's talk about the topic of the show. I think it's a very serious topic. Let's talk about the topic of the show. I think it's a very serious topic. Let's talk about the topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show. The topic of the show.
If you want to go and see me, I will give you a chance. What do you want me to write? I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book. I want to write a book.
You want to learn English? I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English, I want to learn English,
Let's go to the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the capital of the
If you want to learn the language, I can only talk about it. It means that the next generation is coming out. In fact, I heard that the mother said that she wanted to be a young man. Then let us remember that the mother said that the mother had a young man who was born in the life of life.
When we were in our own way, we were able to understand each other. We were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we were able to understand each other every time we
This is not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case. It's not the case.
Come on!